<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<SmellBaseline>
  <ManuallySuppressedIssues></ManuallySuppressedIssues>
  <CurrentIssues>
    <ID>CyclomaticComplexMethod:AppearanceSettingsView.kt$fun PrimaryThemeColor.label(context: ViewContext)</ID>
    <ID>CyclomaticComplexMethod:Base.kt$private inline fun &lt;reified T : Any&gt; NavGraphBuilder.baseComposable( noinline content: @Composable (AnimatedContentScope.(NavBackStackEntry) -&gt; Unit), )</ID>
    <ID>CyclomaticComplexMethod:BottomBar.kt$@OptIn(ExperimentalMaterial3Api::class) @Composable fun NowPlayingBodyBottomBar( context: ViewContext, data: NowPlayingData, states: NowPlayingStates, )</ID>
    <ID>CyclomaticComplexMethod:DebugReceiversRegistrationTest.kt$DebugReceiversRegistrationTest$private fun registrationIsDebugGuarded(source: String, needle: String): Boolean</ID>
    <ID>CyclomaticComplexMethod:FloatInputTile.kt$@OptIn(ExperimentalMaterial3Api::class, ExperimentalLayoutApi::class) @Composable fun SettingsFloatInputTile( context: ViewContext, icon: @Composable () -&gt; Unit, title: @Composable () -&gt; Unit, value: Float, presets: List&lt;Float&gt; = listOf(), labelText: ((Float) -&gt; String) = { it.toString() }, onReset: (() -&gt; Unit)? = null, onChange: (Float) -&gt; Unit, )</ID>
    <ID>CyclomaticComplexMethod:Home.kt$@OptIn(ExperimentalMaterial3Api::class) @Composable fun HomeView(context: ViewContext)</ID>
    <ID>CyclomaticComplexMethod:KordXMediaLibraryService.kt$KordXMediaLibraryService.BrowseTreeCallback$private fun mediaItemForId(mediaId: String): MediaItem?</ID>
    <ID>CyclomaticComplexMethod:RadioSession.kt$RadioSession$fun handlePlayFromMediaId(mediaId: String?, autostart: Boolean = true)</ID>
    <ID>CyclomaticComplexMethod:RadioSession.kt$RadioSession$fun start()</ID>
    <ID>CyclomaticComplexMethod:Search.kt$@OptIn(ExperimentalMaterial3Api::class) @Composable fun SearchView(context: ViewContext, route: SearchViewRoute)</ID>
    <ID>CyclomaticComplexMethod:SongInformationDialog.kt$@Composable fun SongInformationDialog(context: ViewContext, song: Song, onDismissRequest: () -&gt; Unit)</ID>
    <ID>ForEachOnRange:ForYou.kt$0..2</ID>
    <ID>ForEachOnRange:ForYou.kt$3..5</ID>
    <ID>FunctionNaming:SamplingInfoStringTest.kt$SamplingInfoStringTest.&lt;no name provided&gt;$fun XChannels(x: String): String</ID>
    <ID>FunctionNaming:SamplingInfoStringTest.kt$SamplingInfoStringTest.&lt;no name provided&gt;$fun XKHz(x: String): String</ID>
    <ID>FunctionNaming:SamplingInfoStringTest.kt$SamplingInfoStringTest.&lt;no name provided&gt;$fun XKbps(x: String): String</ID>
    <ID>FunctionOnlyReturningConstant:Media3ItemFactory.kt$Media3ItemFactory$fun descriptionForGenre(genre: Genre): String</ID>
    <ID>LargeClass:KordXMediaLibraryService.kt$KordXMediaLibraryService$BrowseTreeCallback : Callback</ID>
    <ID>LongMethod:KordXMediaLibraryService.kt$KordXMediaLibraryService.BrowseTreeCallback$private fun mediaItemForId(mediaId: String): MediaItem?</ID>
    <ID>LongMethod:RadioSession.kt$RadioSession$fun start()</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:ColorScheme.kt$ThemeColorSchemes$// `onBackground` is the value that the; `LocalContentColor` fallback reads from when no other; component overrides it. The previous `adjustLightness(; primaryColor,0.5f)` derives a verydarkpurple for the; default Purple primary, but the derivation depends on the; primary color: a light primary (e.g. pastel yellow) would; produce a darkyellow `onBackground`, which is OK; a; mediumlightness primary (e.g. cyan) would produce a; nearinvisible `onBackground`. The safer value is a fixed; nearblack that's visible on every surface.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:ColorScheme.kt$ThemeColorSchemes$// `onSecondaryContainer` was previously `LightContrastColor`; (pure white). Pure white is the highestcontrast value on dark; surfaces, but it can be visually jarring for body text. Pin; to the offwhite value that matches the default `darkColorScheme()`; `onSurface` (`Color(0xFFE6E1E5)`) so the visual hierarchy is; consistent. The offwhite value is visible on every dark; surface and matches the `LocalContentColor` fallback value; the KordXTheme CompositionLocalProvider also pins.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:ColorScheme.kt$ThemeColorSchemes$// `onSecondaryContainer` was previously unset, which; meant the framework default (`Color(0xFF4A4458)` for; `lightColorScheme()`) was used. The default is dark, so it; was visible on a light surface — but the AVD walkthrough; showed that `FilterChip` selected labels (which use; `onSecondaryContainer`) were still invisible. Pinning it; to the same fixed dark value (the same one used for; `onBackground` / `onSurface` / `onSurfaceVariant`) makes; the chip labels deterministic regardless of the active; primary color. The `DarkOnBackgroundForLightTheme` constant; is used directly (not via `adjustLightness`) because; `adjustLightness` calls `ColorUtils.colorToHSL`, which is; mocked to return 0 in the JVM unittest classpath (per; `unitTests.isReturnDefaultValues = true` in; `app/build.gradle.kts`).</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:ColorScheme.kt$ThemeColorSchemes$// `onSurfaceVariant` is what `FilterChip` (unselected); and `ListItem` (supporting text) read for their text color.; Pinning it to the same dark value (slightly lighter alpha; for mediumemphasis) keeps the chip labels visible.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:ColorScheme.kt$ThemeColorSchemes$// fixed visible value for the dark / black theme's; textondark tokens. The default `darkColorScheme()` uses; `Color(0xFFE6E1E5)` (offwhite) which is visible on every dark; surface. Pinning to that same value makes the surface text; deterministic.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:ColorScheme.kt$ThemeColorSchemes$// fixed visible value for the light theme's textonlight; tokens (`onBackground` / `onSurface` / `onSurfaceVariant`). The; default `lightColorScheme()` uses `Color(0xFF1C1B1F)` (very dark; gray) which is visible on every light surface. We pin to that; same nearblack value (with a slight tint of the primary color; for brand consistency, matching the `onBackground` value the; Material3 default would produce for the default Purple primary).; Critically: this is INDEPENDENT of the user's primary color, so; a light primary (e.g. yellow) doesn't produce a nearinvisible; text color. This is the value that the [LocalContentColor]; CompositionLocalProvider in `KordXTheme` also pins, so both; paths agree.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:ColorScheme.kt$ThemeColorSchemes$// same as `createDarkColorScheme`. The BLACK theme; uses pure black surfaces (`background = Color.Black`), so the; text color must be light. `LightOnBackgroundForDarkTheme`; (offwhite) is visible on pure black.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:ColorScheme.kt$ThemeColorSchemes$// same reasoning as `onBackground`: `onSurface` is; the value that Material3 `Surface` propagates into; `LocalContentColor` for any text inside the surface. A; fixed dark value is visible on every light surface.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:ColorSchemeVisibilityTest.kt$ColorSchemeVisibilityTest$/** JVM unit tests that pin the visibility of the critical text-on-surface ColorScheme tokens for all 3 KordX themes (light / dark / black). **Important context:** the KordX test classpath sets `unitTests.isReturnDefaultValues = true` (see `app/build.gradle.kts`). This makes unmocked framework methods (e.g. `ColorUtils.blendARGB`) return their default values (0) instead of executing the real implementation. The light theme's `onBackground` was derived from the primary color via the `blendColors` helper (which itself uses `ColorUtils.blendARGB`); on the test classpath this returns 0 (transparent black), which is exactly the same bug the production code exhibited (an invisible text color in the `lightColorScheme()` default). The fix replaces the `blendColors`-derived `onBackground` with a fixed `Color(0xFF1C1B1F)` (Material3 default dark text), which is INDEPENDENT of `ColorUtils.blendARGB` and therefore works correctly on the test classpath. The test asserts: 1. The `onBackground` token for the LIGHT theme is the fixed near-black value `Color(0xFF1C1B1F)` (NOT the derived value from the primary color). 2. The `onBackground` value is the same regardless of the primary color (a light primary no longer produces a near-invisible text color). 3. The `onBackground` token has non-zero alpha (not transparent). 4. The `onSurface` token for the LIGHT theme is the same fixed near-black value. 5. The `onSurfaceVariant` token for the LIGHT theme is the same fixed near-black value. 6. The `onSecondaryContainer` token for the LIGHT theme is the same fixed near-black value. 7. The DARK / BLACK themes' `onBackground` is the fixed off-white value `Color(0xFFE6E1E5)`. 8. The DARK / BLACK themes' `onSurface` / `onSurfaceVariant` / `onSecondaryContainer` are the same fixed off-white value. (The pre-30i values: `onBackground` was `adjustLightness( primaryColor, -0.5f)` which derives a near-black dark color from the primary; `onSurface` was the same; `onSurfaceVariant` was `adjustLightness(primaryColor, -0.45f)` which derives a slightly lighter dark color from the primary; `onSecondaryContainer` was unset, so it fell through to the Material3 default `Color(0xFF4A4458)`. The fix pins all 4 to the same fixed `Color(0xFF1C1B1F)` for the light theme so the text is visible regardless of the user's primary color.) */</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:ColorSchemeVisibilityTest.kt$ColorSchemeVisibilityTest$// The text color is the same regardless of the primary color; (the whole point of the fix: a light primary no longer; produces a nearinvisible text color).</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:CustomBrowseActionTest.kt$CustomBrowseActionTest$/** JVM unit tests for the root-level custom browse actions built by [RadioSessionState.shuffleAllAction], [RadioSessionState.searchAction], and [RadioSessionState.rootCustomActions]. The builders are pure data — no `KordX`, no `Radio`, no Android `Uri` / `Bundle` / `MediaSessionCompat` — so the whole surface is testable on the JVM without an emulator. The tests pin: - The 2 `ACTION_*` constants match the namespaced values. - The `shuffleAllAction()` builder returns the right `action` / icon / label. - The `searchAction()` builder returns the right `action` / icon / label. - The `rootCustomActions()` list is exactly `[shuffleAll, search]` in that order, and is deterministic (same input → same output). - The hide/show audit: no `KordXMediaLibraryService` source-file path contains the banned terms (Settings, About, Equalizer, Sleep timer, Crossfade, Discord, Reddit, GitHub issue, Update check, Onboarding, Theme picker, Language picker, Cast, Bluetooth picker). The test greps the source file for each banned term and asserts zero matches. */</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:CustomBrowseActionTest.kt$CustomBrowseActionTest$// The plan: "No MediaItem in the browse tree exposes:; Settings, About, Equalizer, Sleep timer, Crossfade,; Community links (Discord / Reddit / GitHub reportissue),; Update check, Onboarding / help, Theme picker, Language; picker, Cast / Bluetooth picker." This test greps the; active mediabrowser service source for the banned; terms and asserts zero matches. As of 26i the active; service is the AndroidX Media3; `KordXMediaLibraryService` (the legacy; `KordXMediaBrowserService` was deleted in the 26i; cutover). The grep is casesensitive on the term; itself but tolerates surrounding word characters; (e.g. "SettingsActivity" is still a match — theanned; term is the substring "Settings").</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:CustomBrowseActionTest.kt$CustomBrowseActionTest$// The test reads the source file from disk because the; JVM unittest classpath doesn't include the; `app/src/main/` source tree as compiled classes. JVM; tests run with the working directory as the module root; (i.e. `app/`), so the relative path is `src/main/...`.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:CustomBrowseActionTest.kt$CustomBrowseActionTest$// Unlike `allCustomActions(shuffleOn, loopMode, isFavorite)`,; `rootCustomActions` takes no parameters. Verified by the; empty argument list below — if the signature ever changes to; require state, this test fails.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:DebugReceiversRegistrationTest.kt$DebugReceiversRegistrationTest$// Extract the `fun start()` body. The FIRST `registerReceiver(`; call in start() is the production `receiver`. It should NOT be; preceded by `if (BuildConfig.DEBUG)`.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:DebugReceiversRegistrationTest.kt$DebugReceiversRegistrationTest$// The BroadcastReceiver.onReceive{} bodies should NOT be wrapped; in BuildConfig.DEBUG — they only fire when the receiver is; registered (which IS gated). Gating the handler body as well; would be redundant and confusing.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:DebugReceiversRegistrationTest.kt$DebugReceiversRegistrationTest$// The debugCustomActionReceiver registration should be inside a; `if (BuildConfig.DEBUG) {` block. Search for the registration; pattern, not just the receiver name (which also appears in the; val definition).</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:ForYou.kt$// use the existing AlbumArtistTile (already renders; name text below the artwork) instead of the inline; `Card { AsyncImage }` that previously had no text at all.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:ForYou.kt$// use the existing AlbumTile (already renders title +; artist text below the artwork) instead of the inline; `Card { AsyncImage }` that previously had no text at all.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:ForYou.kt$// use the existing ArtistTile (already renders name; text below the artwork) instead of the inline; `Card { AsyncImage }` that previously had no text at all.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:ForYouTextLabelsTest.kt$ForYouTextLabelsTest$/** JVM unit test that confirms [ForYou.kt] no longer contains the standalone `Card { AsyncImage }` pattern under the `SuggestedAlbums` / `SuggestedArtists` / `SuggestedAlbumArtists` private composables. The old code rendered 6 anonymous tiles (artwork only, no album/artist name) because the inline `Card { AsyncImage }` had no `Text` composable inside. The fix replaces those 3 inline `Card { AsyncImage }` blocks with calls to the existing [AlbumTile] / [ArtistTile] / [AlbumArtistTile] composables, which already render title + artist text correctly. The Albums / Artists / Album Artists tabs already used these tile composables (and rendered correctly on the AVD), so reusing them here is the lowest-risk fix. The test greps the source file for the three old patterns (one per Suggested composable) and asserts: 1. None of the inline `Card { AsyncImage }` patterns exist under the `Suggested*` composables. 2. The new `AlbumTile` / `ArtistTile` / `AlbumArtistTile` call sites are present (regression guard against accidental reverts). Mirrors the source-level test pattern from 's `RadioQueueLoopShufflePersistenceTest`, 's `CustomBrowseActionTest`, and 's `IconRefinementTest`: the test reads the .kt file from disk and asserts the regression-critical structural changes are present. */</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:ForYouTextLabelsTest.kt$ForYouTextLabelsTest$// Match a `Card(` immediately followed (after whitespace) by an; `AsyncImage(` inside the `SuggestedAlbums` composable block.; The block ends at the closing `}` of the composable.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:GrooveModelExtensions.kt$// + 30k — there30e version used; val values = mutableListOf&lt;String&gt;(); encoder?.let { values.add(it) }; channels?.let { values.add(kordx.t.XChannels(it.toString())) }; bitrateK?.let { values.add(buildString { append(kordx.t.XKbps(it.toString())) }) }; samplingRateK?.let { values.add(kordx.t.XKHz(it.toString())) }; return values.takeIf { it.isNotEmpty() }?.joinToString(", ")</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:GrooveModelExtensions.kt$// Extension functions that bridge the pure data models in :core with the; KordX service layer. Kept here so :core stays free of appshell dependencies.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:GrooveModelExtensions.kt$// The fix uses `listOfNotNull(...)` (declarative, no mutable; accumulator) AND wraps each `?.let { ... }` in `.takeIf {; it.isNotBlank() }` so any empty / blank formatted string is; also filtered out. The result is a stable `Lavf57.82.101`only; string for the FLAC case (instead of `Lavf57.82.101, , ,`).</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:IconRefinementTest.kt$IconRefinementTest$/** JVM unit tests for the icon refinement. Verifies that all 10 icons referenced by the -22 custom action paths + the /8 launcher icon set exist as valid vector drawable XML files in the resource directory, and that the refinements (RTL auto-mirroring, brand-consistent coloring) are present. The 10 icons audited: 1. `ic_shuffle` — Now Playing card custom action 2. `ic_shuffle_active` — Now Playing card custom action 3. `ic_repeat` — Now Playing card custom action 4. `ic_repeat_active` — Now Playing card custom action 5. `ic_repeat_one` — Now Playing card custom action 6. `ic_favorite_border` — Now Playing card custom action 7. `ic_favorite_filled` — Now Playing card custom action 8. `ic_search` — root browse action 9. `ic_launcher_foreground` — /8 adaptive icon foreground 10. `ic_launcher_monochrome` — Android 13+ themed icon The tests are source-level (read the .xml from disk) because the Android resource system is not available on the JVM unit-test classpath (the same constraint documented in the `KordXMediaLibraryServiceTest` + the hardening notes). The runtime behavior is verified on the AVD via the existing -22 `DEBUG_ACTION_*` debug-broadcast receivers, which exercise the same `Resources.getIdentifier(name, "drawable", ...)` code path that the Now Playing card + root browse actions use. */</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:IconRefinementTest.kt$IconRefinementTest$// Regression guard: the icons referenced by the RadioSession; custom actions + root browse actions must; match the file names. If refactor renames a file,; the `RadioSessionStateTest.iconResolution_*` tests will; catch the runtime failure; this test catches the buildtime; failure (the file is missing from the drawable directory).</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:IconRefinementTest.kt$IconRefinementTest$// The drawable directory is `app/src/main/res/drawable/` for; the default density. Higherdensity variants would live in; `drawablehdpi/`, `drawablexhdpi/`, etc.; for vector; drawables (which is what all 10 icons are), the default; `drawable/` directory is sufficient — vector drawables; scale automatically at all densities.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:IconRefinementTest.kt$IconRefinementTest$// refinement: all action icons set; `android:autoMirrored="true"` so the icon mirrors correctly; for RTL languages (Arabic, Hebrew, etc.). The; `autoMirrored` attribute is a noop for bilaterallysymmetric; shapes (heart, search) but kept for consistency.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:IconRefinementTest.kt$IconRefinementTest$// refinement: every action icon declares; `android:tint="?attr/colorControlNormal"` so the icon; inherits the theme's `colorControlNormal` (which is; automatically darkonlight or lightondark per the; system theme). The hardcoded `fillColor` is the path's; intrinsic color, which the tint multiplies.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:IconRefinementTest.kt$IconRefinementTest$// refinement: the "active" state icons (shuffle on,; repeat on / repeat one) use the KordX brand cyan #FF00F0FF; instead of the offstate white #FFFFFFFF. This is the; visual signal for "this toggle is on".</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:IconRefinementTest.kt$IconRefinementTest$// refinement: the monochrome variant is intended; for Android 13+ themed icons, so the path colors are; removed (the system applies the theme color via the; `&lt;adaptiveicon&gt;` background/foreground layer).</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:IconRefinementTest.kt$IconRefinementTest$// the filled heart uses Material Design's standard; pink #FFE91E63 (matches the Material 3 "error" color; family) instead of the brand cyan. This is the standard; Material Design convention for "favorited" — theser; expects a pink filled heart universally.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:IconRefinementTest.kt$IconRefinementTest$// the offstate icons (shuffle off, repeat off,; favorite border, search) use white #FFFFFFFF as the; intrinsic fillColor, which the `?attr/colorControlNormal`; tint multiplies to the theme color.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:KordXMediaLibraryService.kt$KordXMediaLibraryService$// 26g — publish the 3 Now Playing card custom actions; (shuffle / repeat / favorite) via `setMediaButtonPreferences`.; The buttons are rebuilt on every relevant `Player.Listener`; event (see [refreshNowPlayingButtons]); the initial publish; here surfaces the buttons on AAOS / Auto from the moment; the framework binds to the service. State defaults to; "no shuffle / no loop / not favorite" because the 26c26h; parallelrun phase uses [NoOpRadioAdapterTarget] (no live; playback); the legacy `RadioSession` continues to drive; playback during this phase and the 26i cutover will switch; to the real `KordX.radio` state lookup.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:KordXMediaLibraryService.kt$KordXMediaLibraryService$// 26h — publish the 2 rootlevel custom browse actions; (SHUFFLE_ALL + SEARCH) via `setCustomLayout`. AAOS; surfaces these buttons at the root of the browse tree; (vs. the Now Playing card, which uses; `setMediaButtonPreferences`). This is the; 26 deliverable — the 2 root actions are now exposed at; the root of the AAOS browse tree, not on the Now Playing; card. The button list is static (no live state — both; "Shuffle all" and "Search" are always available),; so a single `setCustomLayout` call at session creation; is sufficient (the legacy `MediaSession.setCustomLayout`; accepted a `List&lt;PlaybackStateCompat.CustomAction&gt;` — the; Media3 equivalent accepts a `List&lt;CommandButton&gt;`; the; migration is APIshapeonly, the dispatch back to; `RadioSession.handleCustomAction` is unchanged).</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:KordXMediaLibraryService.kt$KordXMediaLibraryService$// 26i — register the 2 debug receivers (DEBUG_ACTION_SCAN +; DEBUG_ACTION_SONG_LIST) so the AVD validation gate can; exercise the 26f placeholders under the new service. The; remaining 8 `DEBUG_ACTION_*` receivers (the 1822 batch); land in 26k.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:KordXMediaLibraryService.kt$KordXMediaLibraryService$// 26i: the 2 debug receivers (DEBUG_ACTION_SCAN +; DEBUG_ACTION_SONG_LIST) ported from the legacy; `KordXMediaBrowserService`. The receivers are registered; in [onCreate] and unregistered in [onDestroy]. They; drive the AVD validation gate for the 26f placeholders; (the "scanning" + "no_songs" + "nothing_recent" rows; exercise the receiverdriven librarystate changes).; The plan calls out reregistration in 26k; the; 26i cutover does it here so the legacy service can be; deleted without losing the AVD validation path.; The 2 receivers (scan + songlist) cover the 26f; placeholder shortcircuits. The 8 other `DEBUG_ACTION_*`; receivers (shuffle / repeat / favorite / shuffle_all /; search / recent_play / playback_error / root_search); land in 26k (they drive the 1822 AVD validation; gates; the new service's handlers are wired in 26i for; shuffle / repeat / favorite / shuffle_all / search via; [BrowseTreeCallback.onCustomCommand], and 26k adds the; broadcastdriven debug entry points).</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:KordXMediaLibraryService.kt$KordXMediaLibraryService$// ====================================================================; BrowseTreeCallback — theeal 26d MediaLibrarySession.Callback; implementation. Owns the 4 browsetree callbacks (real) + 2; stubs (onSearch for 26e, onCustomCommand for 26h) + the; 6 tab builders + 5 drilldown builders + the mediaItemForId; lookup.; ====================================================================</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:KordXMediaLibraryService.kt$KordXMediaLibraryService$// ====================================================================; ErrorOnlyCallback — defensive fallback for the (theoretical) case; where KordX.instance is null at onCreate time. The 26d browse tree; builder depends on KordX state; this callback returns errors for; every method so the framework can still bind to the service (it; just sees "not supported" responses for everything).; ====================================================================</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:KordXMediaLibraryService.kt$KordXMediaLibraryService$// ====================================================================; NoOpRadioAdapterTarget + NoOpRadioQueueAdapterTarget +; NoOpRadioShortyAdapterTarget — unchanged from 26c. Kept as private; inner classes (the 26c KordXMediaLibraryService nested them; under SkeletonCallback; for 26d they're lifted out so the; toplevel createPlayer() can reference them without going; through SkeletonCallback — SkeletonCallback is removed in 26d).; ====================================================================</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:KordXMediaLibraryService.kt$KordXMediaLibraryService$// `Builder(this, ...)` is the MediaLibraryServicenested builder; constructor that takes the owning service (instead of a bare; Context). It wires the session into the service's lifecycle so; `onGetSession` will be called by the framework on bind.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:KordXMediaLibraryService.kt$KordXMediaLibraryService.BrowseTreeCallback$// 26e: store the most recent search query per; controller so the framework's later; `onGetSearchResult` calls can look up which query to; execute. AAOS issues one `onSearch` per "search; initiated by the user" gesture, then any number of; `onGetSearchResult` calls (for paging, refresh,; etc.). One inflight search per controller is the; Media3 contract.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:KordXMediaLibraryService.kt$KordXMediaLibraryService.BrowseTreeCallback$// 26f — also shortcircuit to a single; `nonPlayableItem("Nothing played yet", ...)` when the; recentlyplayed cache is empty (no plays yet, or; post `pm clear`). Mirrors the legacy; [KordXMediaBrowserService.buildRecentPlaysTab] behavior.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:KordXMediaLibraryService.kt$KordXMediaLibraryService.BrowseTreeCallback$// 26f — shortcircuit to a single; `nonPlayableItem(EMPTY_REASON_NO_SONGS, ...)` when the; library has zero songs. Mirrors the legacy; [KordXMediaBrowserService.buildRootTabs] behavior.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:KordXMediaLibraryService.kt$KordXMediaLibraryService.BrowseTreeCallback$// 26f — shortcircuit to a single; `nonPlayableItem(EMPTY_REASON_SCANNING, ...)` when a; scan is in progress (`app.groove.song.isUpdating.value`; is true). AAOS shows the live count via the; `EXTRA_KEY_SCAN_COUNT` int on the placeholder's; extras. Mirrors the legacy; [KordXMediaBrowserService.buildSongsTab] behavior.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:KordXMediaLibraryService.kt$KordXMediaLibraryService.BrowseTreeCallback$// 26h/26i: onCustomCommand — theeal SHUFFLE_ALL + SEARCH; customcommand dispatch (plus SHUFFLE / REPEAT / FAVORITE; dispatched from the Now Playing card actions wired in; 26g). The action strings are the same `RadioSessionState.ACTION_*`; constants the legacy `RadioSession.handleCustomAction`; uses; the dispatch logic mirrors the legacy handler; 1:1, with the radio state mutation delegated to the; real `KordX.radio` instance (26i cutover — the 26h; version had stub handlers; the 26i cutover wires; the live `app.radio` / `app.groove` state).</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:KordXMediaLibraryService.kt$KordXMediaLibraryService.BrowseTreeCallback$// 26i: the 3 Now Playing card action handlers (mirror; the legacy `RadioSession.handleCustomAction` contract; for the 3 `RadioSessionState.ACTION_SHUFFLE` /; `ACTION_REPEAT` / `ACTION_FAVORITE` actions). Each; handler delegates to the live `app.radio` /; `app.groove` state and republishes the Now Playing; card buttons via `refreshNowPlayingButtons` so the; AAOS surface reflects the new state immediately.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:KordXMediaLibraryService.kt$KordXMediaLibraryService.BrowseTreeCallback$// ====================================================================; Browse tree builders — ported from KordXMediaBrowserService.; ====================================================================</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:KordXMediaLibraryService.kt$KordXMediaLibraryService.BrowseTreeCallback$// The 3 Now Playing card actions (26g) are also; routed here in the Media3 model — the; `setMediaButtonPreferences` buttons dispatch through; the same `onCustomCommand` path. The handlers; match the legacy `RadioSession.handleCustomAction`; contract 1:1.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:KordXMediaLibraryServiceTest.kt$KordXMediaLibraryServiceTest$// 3. The 7 expected override methods exist on the interface; (a regression guard for accidental signature drift in a; future Media3 bump — if a method is renamed or its; signature changes, the production build fails, but having; an explicit assertion makes the failure mode obvious in; the test report). The 7th method (onGetSearchResult) is; the actual searchresults callback introduced in 26e.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:KordXMediaLibraryServiceTest.kt$KordXMediaLibraryServiceTest$// 3. The onCreate + onDestroy overrides exist (proves the; lifecycle is wired up — theest seam + reflection on the; field would otherwise leave us with an undocumented service; that never builds or releases a session).</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:KordXMediaLibraryServiceTest.kt$KordXMediaLibraryServiceTest$// LOG_TAG is a `const val` in the companion object — in the; JVM bytecode it gets inlined into the call sites and a; private static field remains on the class for the; companion's own use. We can read it via reflection.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:KordXMediaLibraryServiceTest.kt$KordXMediaLibraryServiceTest$// The `internal` modifier in Kotlin mangles the JVM method; name with the module suffix. Use the standard Kotlin; "is there a method with this mangled name" check via; `methods` rather than `getDeclaredMethod` (which throws; on miss).</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:KordXMediaSessionConstants.kt$KordXMediaSessionConstants$/** shared media-id and debug-action constants + the placeholder-reason constants + bundle-key constants used by the active [KordXMediaLibraryService] (the AndroidX Media3 `MediaLibraryService` introduced in 26c, the active service as of 26i). Before 26i the constants lived across two places: the media-id constants lived as a `companion object` on `KordXMediaBrowserService` and the placeholder-reason constants + bundle-key constants lived on the legacy `MediaItemFactory` companion. After 26i both `KordXMediaBrowserService` and `MediaItemFactory` are deleted, so the constants are lifted into this top-level file so the new service can use them without the legacy classes. The `DEBUG_ACTION_*` constants are also lifted (the new service registers the 2 scan + song-list debug receivers in 26i; the remaining 8 `DEBUG_ACTION_*` receivers land in 26k). The constants are `const val`s so they inline at the call site — no runtime cost, no `KordXMediaSessionConstants.` prefix needed if the caller is in the same package (the new service is). Media-id convention (unchanged from ): - [ID_ROOT] root - [ID_TAB_SONGS] all songs (playable leaves) - [ID_TAB_ALBUMS] / [ID_TAB_ARTISTS] / [ID_TAB_GENRES] / [ID_TAB_PLAYLISTS] / [ID_TAB_RECENT] - [PREFIX_ALBUM] + id songs in an album - [PREFIX_ARTIST] + name songs by an artist (alias of albumArtist) - [PREFIX_ALBUM_ARTIST] + name songs by an album artist - [PREFIX_GENRE] + name songs in a genre - [PREFIX_PLAYLIST] + id songs in a playlist - [PREFIX_SONG] + id a single playable song (used by onPlayFromMediaId) */</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:KordXMediaSessionConstants.kt$KordXMediaSessionConstants$// Debug actions (used by the `KordXMediaLibraryService` debug; receivers registered in `onCreate`). The 2 receivers; (scan + songlist) are registered in 26i; the remaining; 8 `DEBUG_ACTION_*` receivers (shuffle / repeat / favorite /; shuffle_all / search / recent_play / playback_error /; root_search) land in 26k.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:KordXMediaSessionConstants.kt$KordXMediaSessionConstants$// Placeholder reason + bundlekey constants (,; frameworkagnostic — used by both the new Media3 service; and the JVM unit tests for `Media3ItemFactory.placeholderExtras`).; The 3 `EMPTY_REASON_*` constants are referenced by the AVD; validation gate's `adb logcatd | grep; "KordXMediaLibraryService.*placeholder:no_songs"` style; filters. Pinning the values in this shared file means a; typo surfaces as a test failure rather than a silent; logcatgrep miss.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:MainActivity.kt$MainActivity$// Typedsearch path: a Bundle with the artist / album /; title / genre / playlist fields AAOS resolved from a; "play the album X" voice command. Compose a single; search query from the populated fields; the fuzzy; search in `KordXSearch` ranks by combined text.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:MainActivity.kt$MainActivity$// forward the `MediaSearchActivity` activityalias; extras (the alias targets this activity; its intentfilter; declares `android.media.action.MEDIA_PLAY_FROM_SEARCH`). The; alias is the production entry point for AAOS's voicesearch; button; without this forwarding the framework delivers the; intent to this activity, the activity opens the Compose UI,; and the query is dropped on the floor (the search runs; through `RadioSession.handlePlayFromSearch`, which is only; wired from `MediaSessionCompat.Callback.onPlayFromSearch` in; the Auto path).</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:MainActivity.kt$MainActivity$// setIntent so any subsequent getIntent() call (e.g. from; a composable that inspects the launch intent) sees the new; intent, not the original coldstart one.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:MainActivityMediaSearchForwardingTest.kt$MainActivityMediaSearchForwardingTest$// Regression guard: the forwarding is an *additional* routing; surface for the alias, not a replacement for the; MediaSession `onPlayFromSearch` callback that; `RadioSession.start()` wires. The MediaSession callback; is the path AAOS uses when the user is actively in the; Auto UI and presses the voice button there; the alias is; the path used when Auto routes the voice search through; the system media search intent. Both must remain.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:MainActivityMediaSearchForwardingTest.kt$MainActivityMediaSearchForwardingTest$// The MainActivity forwarding must NOT introduce a duplicate; `handlePlayFromSearch` definition in MainActivity.kt; (the routing must stay in RadioSession, not in MainActivity).</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:MainActivityMediaSearchForwardingTest.kt$MainActivityMediaSearchForwardingTest$// The `android.provider.MediaStore` import must be present; so the `MediaStore.INTENT_ACTION_MEDIA_PLAY_FROM_SEARCH` /; `MediaStore.EXTRA_MEDIA_FOCUS` / `MediaStore.EXTRA_MEDIA_TITLE`; references resolve. Regression guard: refactor; that drops the import will break the build, but this test; makes the failure mode obvious (the structural test fails; with a clear "import missing" message first).</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:MainActivityMediaSearchForwardingTest.kt$MainActivityMediaSearchForwardingTest$// The `forwardMediaSearchIntent(intent)` call must be present; in `onNewIntent` so warmstart alias launches retrigger; the forwarding (the plan "onNewIntent: extract ...; extras ... and forward to handlePlayFromSearch").</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:MainActivityMediaSearchForwardingTest.kt$MainActivityMediaSearchForwardingTest$// The `onCreate` body must call `forwardMediaSearchIntent(intent)`; so a coldstart alias launch (e.g. the AVD validation step; `am starta android.intent.action.MEDIA_PLAY_FROM_SEARCHes; query "Moth"`) actually reaches the radio session.; We check both the call is present AND the `intent` parameter; is the activity's `intent` (not a different variable).</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:MainActivityMediaSearchForwardingTest.kt$MainActivityMediaSearchForwardingTest$// The `setIntent(intent)` call must be present in `onNewIntent`; so any subsequent `getIntent()` call (e.g. from a composable; that inspects the launch intent) sees the new intent, not; the original coldstart one.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:MainActivityMediaSearchForwardingTest.kt$MainActivityMediaSearchForwardingTest$// The composed query must include the typedsearch fields; AAOS sends. We assert the four main field keys are read; (title, album, artist, genre; the playlist key is; SoftDeprecated but still functional and is in the source).</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:MainActivityMediaSearchForwardingTest.kt$MainActivityMediaSearchForwardingTest$// The forwarding call must come AFTER `kordx.emitActivityReady()`; so `KordX.instance` is populated when the forward runs (the; forward reads `KordX.instance` via the static `Volatile`; field; a forward before `emitActivityReady` would hit the; nullinstance defensive return and drop the search).</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:MainActivityMediaSearchForwardingTest.kt$MainActivityMediaSearchForwardingTest$// The helper must earlyreturn for any nonMEDIA_PLAY_FROM_SEARCH; action so the standard `MAIN` / `LAUNCHER` launch intent and; any other intents are not touched. We assert both the action; check is present and the right constant is used (the public; `MediaStore.INTENT_ACTION_MEDIA_PLAY_FROM_SEARCH` constant,; not a hardcoded string — keeps the test aligned with the; SDK's canonical action string).</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:MainActivityMediaSearchForwardingTest.kt$MainActivityMediaSearchForwardingTest$// The helper must forward to; `KordX.instance.radio.session.handlePlayFromSearch(query)`.; The static `KordX.instance` access is the liveinstance; pattern the rest of the codebase uses (see; `KordXMediaLibraryService.kt` for the same pattern).</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:MainActivityMediaSearchForwardingTest.kt$MainActivityMediaSearchForwardingTest$// The helper must log the forwarded query so the AVD; validation gate (`adb logcatd | grep "MainActivity.*MEDIA_PLAY_FROM_SEARCH"`); can confirm the forwarding fired. The checklist:; "AVD: `am starta android.intent.action.MEDIA_PLAY_FROM_SEARCH; es query "Moth"` → logcat shows `onPlayFromSearch: query='Moth'`"; — that log line comes from RadioSession.handlePlayFromSearch; MainActivity's own log line is the complementary gate that; confirms the routing happened.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:MainActivityMediaSearchForwardingTest.kt$MainActivityMediaSearchForwardingTest$// The helper must read `MediaStore.EXTRA_MEDIA_FOCUS` (a Bundle; holding the typedsearch fields — AAOS's "play the album X"; path). We assert the getBundleExtra call is present and is; routed to the typedsearch composition path.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:MainActivityMediaSearchForwardingTest.kt$MainActivityMediaSearchForwardingTest$// The helper must tolerate a `null` `KordX.instance` (e.g.; an `am start` race before `KordX` finishes initializing); by logging + returning without crashing. The activity is; the `singleTask` root, so a crash here would blackhole; the framework; the defensive return is intentional.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:MainActivityMediaSearchForwardingTest.kt$MainActivityMediaSearchForwardingTest$// The manifest's `MediaSearchActivity` activityalias is the; trigger for the forwarding — verify the alias still targets; `MainActivity` and still declares the; `android.media.action.MEDIA_PLAY_FROM_SEARCH` intent filter.; ( doesn't change the manifest; this is a regression; guard so manifest edit doesn't accidentally; remove the trigger and silently disable the forwarding.)</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:MainActivityMediaSearchForwardingTest.kt$MainActivityMediaSearchForwardingTest$// The nullinstance path must log (so the AVD validation gate; can confirm the defensive return fired if KordX is ever; null at the right time).</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:MainActivityMediaSearchForwardingTest.kt$MainActivityMediaSearchForwardingTest$// Whitespacetolerant: a regex that matches `Logger.warn(`; followed by any whitespace, then `"MainActivity"`. A future; refactor that reindents the call site must not break this; assertion.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:Media3ItemFactory.kt$Media3ItemFactory$/** + 26i — Builders for the AndroidX Media3 browse tree of the new [KordXMediaLibraryService]. The 26i cutover inlines the per-entity display-contract data (the `descriptionForSong` / `songSubtitle` / `songExtras` / `albumSubtitle` / etc. helpers) from the deleted legacy `MediaItemFactory` so the new service has a single self-contained Media3 `MediaItem` factory. The `Extras` data class + the constants + the placeholder helper live in the new shared [KordXMediaSessionConstants] file (also a 26i extraction). Why one factory (not two) Before 26i the codebase had two parallel factories: `MediaItemFactory` (producing the legacy `MediaBrowserCompat.MediaItem` for the -22 `KordXMediaBrowserService`) and `Media3ItemFactory` (producing the Media3 `MediaItem` for the new service). They shared the same data layer (the per-entity display contract is framework-agnostic). After 26i the legacy service is gone, so the legacy factory is gone too — theer-entity data is inlined here, and the new factory produces Media3 `MediaItem` instances directly. Media3 MediaItem shape A Media3 `MediaItem` carries its display fields (`title` / `subtitle` / `description` / `iconUri` / `extras` / `isBrowsable` / `isPlayable` / `mediaType`) on the inner `MediaMetadata`, not on the `MediaItem` itself. The factory below always sets both: - `MediaItem.Builder().setMediaId(id).setMediaMetadata(metadata)` — thetem-level mediaId is what the framework routes on. - `MediaMetadata.Builder().setTitle(title).setSubtitle(subtitle)… .setIsBrowsable(b).setIsPlayable(p).setMediaType(t).setExtras(b)` — theetadata-level fields are what the framework renders. The `setUri(...)` builder method is intentionally **not** called — the songs are routed through `KordXMediaSessionConstants.mediaIdToSongId` + the live `KordX.groove.song.get(id)` lookup, not through an `ExoPlayer.setMediaItem(uri)` path. Unstable API Marked `@UnstableApi` because `MediaItem` and `MediaMetadata` are part of Media3's unstable surface (subject to API breakage between minor versions). The plan (26a-26m) commits to the 1.7.1 API; Media3 upgrade (1.10.x requires `compileSdk = 36`) will be handled */</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:Media3ItemFactory.kt$Media3ItemFactory$// Perentity adapters: take a live Song/Album/etc. and produce; the corresponding Media3 MediaItem with the full display; contract. These are the entry points the new; KordXMediaLibraryService.MediaLibrarySession.Callback uses; to build the browse tree.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:Media3ItemFactoryTest.kt$Media3ItemFactoryTest$/** JVM unit tests for the Media3-flavored [Media3ItemFactory]. The factory is parallel to the legacy [MediaItemFactory] (which produces the support-library `MediaBrowserCompat.MediaItem` for the -22 `KordXMediaBrowserService`); the new factory produces Media3 `MediaItem` instances for the new `KordXMediaLibraryService`. What this test exercises The Media3 `MediaItem` + `MediaMetadata` builders are pure (no Android `Uri`, no `KordX`, no `Context`), so the bulk of the factory is JVM-testable on the Android stub classpath: 1. **Media3-specific builder sanity** (`browsable` / `playable` / `nonPlayable` set `isBrowsable` / `isPlayable` / `mediaType` / `mediaId` / `title` / `subtitle` / `description` round-trip through the `MediaMetadata` builder). The Bundle round-trip for `extras` is verified at the data class level by the legacy `MediaItemFactoryTest` (the data flows through `Media3ItemFactory.Extras.toBundle()` unchanged — see the / 21 bundle-shape note in that file's KDoc). 2. **Per-entity display contract** (delegated to [MediaItemFactory] — theescriptions / subtitles / extras data is the same as the legacy service's, and the JVM tests for that data already live in [MediaItemFactoryTest]). The new tests in this file focus on the Media3 wiring of that data: a `browsableAlbum(...)` carries the right `MEDIA_TYPE_FOLDER_ALBUMS`, the `albumExtras` data is the right shape, etc. 3. **Tab-level extras** (the `*TabExtras` helpers — `songsTabExtras`, `albumsTabExtras`, etc. — produce the same `Media3ItemFactory.Extras` data the legacy factory produces, mirrored verbatim in [MediaItemFactoryTest]). What this test does NOT cover The per-Song adapter ([Media3ItemFactory.playableSongItem]) is NOT tested here. `Song`'s constructor requires a non-null `android.net.Uri`, and the Android stub jar used in JVM unit tests returns `null` from `Uri.parse` / `Uri.EMPTY` and throws "Method ... not mocked" from any Uri method call. The `MediaItemFactoryTest` file has the same Song-construction constraint documented in its kdoc, and the per-Song display contract is covered by inspection of the `KordXMediaBrowserService` `buildSongsTab` / `songIdsToPlayableItems` code paths plus the legacy tests for the `descriptionForSong` / `songSubtitle` / `songExtras` pure-helper data. The Media3 wiring of the `playableSongItem` builder is the same as `playable(...)` plus the per-entity factories — both halves are tested here, so the integration is structurally sound. The `MediaMetadata.extras` Bundle is NOT inspected here because the Android stub jar used in JVM unit tests throws `RuntimeException("Method ... in android.os.Bundle not mocked")` from any `Bundle.getString` / `getInt` / `getLong` call. The underlying `Media3ItemFactory.Extras` data class (the source of every key/value that goes into the Bundle) is fully tested by the parallel `MediaItemFactoryTest` — so the data is correct end-to-end; we just skip the Bundle round-trip in this file. */</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:Media3ItemFactoryTest.kt$Media3ItemFactoryTest$// 26f — the 3rd placeholder reason (the playbackerror; path). The plan: "EMPTY_REASON_ERROR: the playback; error path. The RadioSession error handler surfaces this; when handlePlayFromMediaId / handlePlayFromSearch catches; an exception from RadioShorty.playQueue. The count; argument is ignored for this reason." So the extras; carry the reason string under `EXTRA_KEY_EMPTY_REASON`; and have no `EXTRA_KEY_SCAN_COUNT` (the error placeholder; doesn't track a count).</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:Media3ItemFactoryTest.kt$Media3ItemFactoryTest$// 26f — the `nonPlayable` Media3 MediaItem shape is the; right shape for the empty / scanning / error placeholders; (the user can't tap it to drill in, and tapping it; doesn't start playback). Verify the 3 placeholdershape; requirements: isBrowsable = false, isPlayable = false,; and a placeholder mediaId is preserved.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:Media3ItemFactoryTest.kt$Media3ItemFactoryTest$// ================================================================; Delegation invariants (the Media3 factory must delegate the; perentity display contract to the legacy factory, so the; /19/20/21 contract is preserved 1:1 across both; services).; ================================================================</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:Media3ItemFactoryTest.kt$Media3ItemFactoryTest$// ================================================================; Media3specific builder sanity (MediaItem + MediaMetadata wiring).; ================================================================</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:Media3ItemFactoryTest.kt$Media3ItemFactoryTest$// ================================================================; Perentity adapters (no Song — Album/AlbumArtist/Genre/Playlist only).; ================================================================</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:Media3ItemFactoryTest.kt$Media3ItemFactoryTest$// ================================================================; Perentity displaycontract data (delegated to MediaItemFactory).; ================================================================</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:Media3ItemFactoryTest.kt$Media3ItemFactoryTest$// ================================================================; Tablevel extras (delegated to MediaItemFactory).; ================================================================</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:Media3ItemFactoryTest.kt$Media3ItemFactoryTest$// ================================================================; placeholderExtras — passthrough to MediaItemFactory.; ================================================================</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:Media3ItemFactoryTest.kt$Media3ItemFactoryTest$// ================================================================; songExtrasWithPlayedAt — 's additive helper.; ================================================================</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:Media3ItemFactoryTest.kt$Media3ItemFactoryTest$// Defensive: even if a caller passes a `count` to the error; placeholder, the resulting extras must not carry; `EXTRA_KEY_SCAN_COUNT` (the count is scanningspecific).</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:Media3ItemFactoryTest.kt$Media3ItemFactoryTest$// Mirrors MediaItemFactoryTest.albumsTabExtrasOverrideToGrid; — the Media3 factory delegates the data to the legacy; factory, so the perentity extras are identical.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:Media3ItemFactoryTest.kt$Media3ItemFactoryTest$// Pin the delegation: the Media3 factory must produce; exactly the same `Media3ItemFactory.Extras` data the; legacy factory produces. This is the structural; invariant that keeps the display contract; consistent between the two services.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:Media3ItemFactoryTest.kt$Media3ItemFactoryTest$// See `browsableAlbum_setsMediaTypeFolderAlbumsAndCarriesDisplayData`; for why we test the delegation invariant on the data; class instead of calling the perentity factory; (Extras.toBundle → BaseBundle.putInt is not mocked).</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:Media3ItemFactoryTest.kt$Media3ItemFactoryTest$// The 3 `EMPTY_REASON_*` constants are referenced by the; plan + the AVD validation gate's; `adb logcatd | grep "KordXMediaLibraryService.*placeholder:no_songs"`; style filters. Pin the values so a typo surfaces as a; test failure rather than a silent logcatgrep miss.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:Media3ItemFactoryTest.kt$Media3ItemFactoryTest$// The Bundle is not inspectable on the JVM (the Android; stub jar throws "not mocked" from any Bundle method; call), so we verify the `createdAt` flows through the; underlying `Media3ItemFactory.Extras` data class — the; same code path the Bundle roundtrip uses at runtime.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:Media3ItemFactoryTest.kt$Media3ItemFactoryTest$// The PLAYED_AT extra key is referenced by the plan; (the AVD validation gate's; `adb logcatd | grep "KordXMediaLibraryService.*PLAYED_AT"`; is one of the 26l evidence lines) — pin the value; so a typo would surface as a test failure rather than a; silent logcatgrep miss.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:Media3ItemFactoryTest.kt$Media3ItemFactoryTest$// The `EXTRA_KEY_EMPTY_REASON` + `EXTRA_KEY_SCAN_COUNT`; constants are referenced by the plan+ the AVD; validation gate. Pin the values so a typo surfaces as a; test failure.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:Media3ItemFactoryTest.kt$Media3ItemFactoryTest$// The pertab `browsableTab(...)` builder is the entry; point the BrowseTreeCallback uses for the 6 root tabs.; Verify it sets the right mediaType for the Albums tab; (FOLDER_ALBUMS). We pass `Extras.EMPTY` here (not the; real `albumsTabExtras()` data) because the; `Extras.toBundle()` path goes through Android's; `BaseBundle.putInt` — which is not mocked in the JVM; unittest classpath. The `albumsTabExtras()` data is; fully tested by `MediaItemFactoryTest.albumsTabExtrasOverrideToGrid`; and our `perEntityFactoriesDelegateToMediaItemFactory`; test below.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:Media3ItemFactoryTest.kt$Media3ItemFactoryTest$// We can't call `browsableAlbum(...)` here because the; perentity `albumExtras` data is nonempty and the; `Extras.toBundle()` path goes through Android's; `BaseBundle.putString` — which is not mocked in the JVM; unittest classpath. The perentity `browsableAlbum`; wiring (mediaId / mediaType / title) is verified; by inspection of the BrowseTreeCallback.buildAlbumsTab; code path; the display contract (the `albumExtras`; data) is fully tested by the parallel; `MediaItemFactoryTest.albumExtrasContainYearTrackCountAndAlbumArtist`; + `albumSubtitleUsesPrimaryArtist` +; `albumDescriptionIncludesYearTracksAndDuration` tests.; The `perEntityFactoriesDelegateToMediaItemFactory`; test below pins the delegation invariant: the perentity; factory must use the same `albumExtras` data as the; legacy factory.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:Media3ItemFactoryTest.kt$Media3ItemFactoryTest$// We can't construct a Song (Uri constraint), so we test; the additive `withLong` behavior on a bare Extras; instance — theame code path `songExtrasWithPlayedAt`; uses internally. (The full Songroundtrip is covered; by inspection of `BrowseTreeCallback.buildRecentPlaysTab`; + the legacy `withLong` KUnit tests on the; `Media3ItemFactory.Extras` data class itself in; `MediaItemFactoryTest.extrasExposeAllEntryKinds`.)</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:Media3ItemFactoryTest.kt$Media3ItemFactoryTest$// When `count` is null, the scanning placeholder doesn't; carry the `EXTRA_KEY_SCAN_COUNT` int (the live count; isn't known yet). Verified at the data class level; (the Bundle roundtrip is not inspectable on the JVM —; see the filelevel KDoc).</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:MediaExposer.kt$MediaExposer$// Repositories use ConcurrentHashMap + MutableStateFlow (both threadsafe),; so songs can be emitted on the IO dispatcher without a mainthread hop.; This avoids thousands of mainthread context switches during a scan and; keeps the UI responsive while the library is being indexed.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:NowPlayingIconButtonsA11yTest.kt$NowPlayingIconButtonsA11yTest$/** JVM unit test that scans the NowPlaying + Home view source files for any `IconButton { Icon(..., null, ...) }` pattern and asserts that every such pattern has been replaced with a non-null `contentDescription` argument. The code had 7 IconButton-only controls with `Icon(icon, null)` (no a11y label), which made the NowPlaying screen + the Home overflow menu unusable for TalkBack users: 1. NowPlaying BottomBar — lyrics (Icons.AutoMirrored.Outlined.Article) 2. NowPlaying BottomBar — repeat / repeat-one 3. NowPlaying BottomBar — shuffle (Icons.Filled.Shuffle) 4. NowPlaying BottomBar — more (Icons.Outlined.MoreHoriz) 5. NowPlaying AppBar (regular + landscape) — expand-more 6. NowPlaying BodyContent — favorite / favorite-border 7. NowPlaying BodyContent — more-vert 8. Home top bar — more-vert overflow menu The fix replaces every `Icon(icon, null, ...)` (inside an `IconButton { ... }` block) with `Icon(icon, context.kordx.t.&lt;i18nKey&gt;, ...)`, using the new 5 i18n keys added (`Lyrics`, `Repeat`, `Shuffle`, `More`, `CollapseNowPlaying`, `Favorite`). The test is a source-level scanner (mirrors the pattern from 's `RadioQueueLoopShufflePersistenceTest`, 's `CustomBrowseActionTest`, and 's `IconRefinementTest`). It reads the .kt file from disk and asserts the regression- critical structural changes are present. This is the right pattern because the Android resource system is not available on the JVM unit-test classpath. **Note:** the test only checks `Icon` calls inside `IconButton` blocks. `Icon` calls inside `ListItem { leadingContent = { Icon( ..., null) } }` are NOT audited — the `ListItem` provides its own a11y label via the `headlineContent` `Text` composable, so the leadingContent icon can safely be decorative. */</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:PoppinsFontAliasTest.kt$PoppinsFontAliasTest$/** JVM unit test that pins the [KordXBuiltinFonts.Poppins] alias to the `poppins_*.ttf` font resources (not the `roboto_*.ttf` ones it was previously incorrectly referencing). The `KordXBuiltinFonts.Poppins` was a copy-paste bug from when the Poppins ttf files were added under `app/src/main/res/font/poppins_*.ttf` but the FontFamily reference in [KordXBuiltinFonts.Poppins] was never updated. Users who selected "Poppins" in `settings.fontFamily` got Roboto silently. The test asserts: 1. The Poppins and Roboto `FontFamily` instances are NOT the same object (i.e. the alias was actually updated, not just left pointing at Roboto). 2. The Poppins `FontFamily` resolves to the `R.font.poppins_*` resources (i.e. it's wired to the right font files). 3. The source file [Typography.kt] no longer contains `R.font.roboto_regular` / `R.font.roboto_bold` references inside the Poppins `KordXFont.fromValue(...)` block. The source-level check (#3) is the strongest regression guard: it catches both the original bug (Roboto reference) and regression (re-pasting Roboto) regardless of how the FontFamily instance is exposed. */</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:PoppinsFontAliasTest.kt$PoppinsFontAliasTest$// Sourcelevel check: the Poppins block in Typography.kt must; not contain `R.font.roboto_regular` or `R.font.roboto_bold`; as ACTUAL FONT references (i.e. inside `Font(R.font.roboto_*`).; The block may contain `roboto_regular` in a comment that; explains the pre30b bug, which is fine.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:PoppinsFontAliasTest.kt$PoppinsFontAliasTest$// Sourcelevel check: the Poppins block must reference; `R.font.poppins_regular` and `R.font.poppins_bold`. Catches; an overcorrection (e.g. accidentally pointing at a different; font).</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:PoppinsFontAliasTest.kt$PoppinsFontAliasTest$// Strongest assertion: resolving "Poppins" by name returns a; font whose FontFamily is the same instance as the Poppins; field (not the Roboto one). This catches a regression; where the `all` map is rebuilt with the wrong reference.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:PoppinsFontAliasTest.kt$PoppinsFontAliasTest$// The `KordXTypography.all` map must still include all 5; builtin fonts. If the Poppins entry was accidentally; removed during the fix, this fails.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:PoppinsFontAliasTest.kt$PoppinsFontAliasTest$// Two FontFamily instances with different Font resources must; be distinct objects. If they were the same (the pre30b; bug), Poppins would silently render as Roboto.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:Radio.kt$Radio$// Issue #773 / #707: restore the persisted; loop mode and shuffle mode on app start. The; code held these in memory only, so the user's "Repeat; all" / "Shuffle on" choice was lost on every app restart.; The settings are read here (before `attachGrooveListener`; so the order is deterministic), then the queue's; `setLoopMode` / `setShuffleMode` are called with; `persist = false` semantics by way of the `if (existing !=; value) persist` guard inside those methods (a noop write; doesn't repersist the same value).</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:Radio.kt$Radio$// The override uses the concrete [RadioQueue] / [RadioShorty]; types (which implement [RadioQueueAdapterTarget] /; [RadioShortyAdapterTarget]) so existing call sites that; depend on the concrete types — `radio.queue.add(...)`,; `radio.shorty.previous()` — keep compiling. Kotlin permits; covariant override of `val` getters.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:Radio.kt$Radio$// recursion guard. When the requested index; does not resolve to a song AND the caller is not; autoplaying (e.g. "set up the queue, the user will; press play"), we earlyreturn here. The previous; behavior unconditionally called; `onSongFinish(SongFinishSource.Exception)`, which; reenters `play(nextIndex)`. If the queue contains; only stale song ids (e.g. after a library rescan; removed them, but the queue's `currentQueue` still; references the dead ids), this loop recurses; forever → `StackOverflowError` in the radio; service. With this guard, the userdriven "skip to; a nonexistent song" / "playQueue with autostart =; false" paths return cleanly. The `autostart == true`; path (the errorrecovery autoadvance) is preserved; so the existing exceptionflow still works.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:RadioAdapterTarget.kt$RadioAdapterTarget$/** Narrow adapter surface for [Radio]. Lets the [RadioForwardingPlayer] be JVM-testable with a hand-rolled fake (no `KordX`, no `Application`, no `Room`). The real [Radio] class implements this interface in its class header. Tests provide hand-rolled fakes. Kept in a separate file from [Radio] and [RadioForwardingPlayer] so the compilation order doesn't matter (Kotlin compiles file-by-file; if [RadioAdapterTarget] is in the same file as the consumer, the compiler may not see the interface declaration before the consumer's `override` modifiers). */</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:RadioForwardingPlayer.kt$// The adapter target interfaces ([RadioAdapterTarget],; [RadioQueueAdapterTarget], [RadioShortyAdapterTarget]) live in; a separate file ([RadioAdapterTarget.kt]) so the compilation; order doesn't matter — Kotlin compiles files in; alphabetical order, and `Radio.kt` is compiled before; `RadioForwardingPlayer.kt`.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:RadioForwardingPlayer.kt$RadioForwardingPlayer$/** AndroidX Media3 [Player] adapter for KordX's custom [Radio] engine. This is the "heart" of the [androidx.media3.session.MediaLibraryService] migration: every other a [Player] that the new `MediaLibrarySession` can wrap. Why this class exists KordX has a custom playback engine ([Radio], [RadioQueue], [RadioShorty], [RadioPlayer]) with a non-Media3 event surface ([Radio.Events.Player.*], [Radio.Events.Queue.*], [Radio.Events.QueueOption.*]). AndroidX Media3's `MediaLibraryService` / `MediaLibrarySession` only know about the [Player] interface and [Player.Listener] events. This adapter translates one surface to the other. Design The class extends [BasePlayer] rather than implementing [Player] directly because [BasePlayer] provides the `final` default-implementations of the ~50 media-item / navigation methods (e.g. `setMediaItem`, `addMediaItem`, `removeMediaItem`, `clearMediaItems`, `next`, `previous`, `seekToDefaultPosition`, `seekBack`, `seekForward`, `hasPreviousMediaItem`, etc.). Those defaults delegate to a small set of abstract getters (`getCurrentTimeline()`, `getMediaItemCount()`, `getMediaItemAt(i)`, `getCurrentMediaItemIndex()`) and the single protected abstract [seekTo] (which we wire to [Radio.seek]). The remaining ~30 [Player] methods are implemented below to map cleanly to the [Radio] / [RadioShorty] / [RadioQueue] public surface. Concurrency The adapter does not own playback threads. The [Radio] engine is driven by the `KordXMediaLibraryService` which calls `addListener` / `removeListener` from the Media3 session's callback thread. The adapter subscribes to [Radio.onUpdate] in [subscribeToRadio] (lazy, on first listener add) and unsubscribes in [unsubscribeFromRadio] (called from [release]); events are dispatched to listeners via [playerListenerHandler] (the main [Looper] by default) so the listener sees the same threading model as a regular Media3 [Player]. Interface-driven testability The constructor takes [RadioAdapterTarget] (and the smaller [RadioQueueAdapterTarget] / [RadioShortyAdapterTarget]) rather than a concrete [Radio] / `KordX`. The concrete [Radio], [RadioQueue], and [RadioShorty] classes explicitly implement these interfaces in their class headers. Tests provide hand-rolled fakes. This keeps the adapter JVM-testable without instantiating an `Application` / `ViewModel` / `Room` database. Event mapping Each [Radio.Events] subevent is translated to the corresponding [Player] event-flag(s) and a `Player.Events` is built (the `onEvents(player, events)` batched-listener callback is the preferred listener entry point in Media3 1.4+): | [Radio.Events] | [Player] event flags | |---------------------------------------------|---------------------------------------------------------------| | `Player.Staged` / `Started` / `Resumed` | `EVENT_PLAY_WHEN_READY_CHANGED \| EVENT_IS_PLAYING_CHANGED` | | `Player.Paused` | `EVENT_PLAY_WHEN_READY_CHANGED \| EVENT_IS_PLAYING_CHANGED` | | `Player.Stopped` | `EVENT_PLAYBACK_STATE_CHANGED \| EVENT_IS_PLAYING_CHANGED` | | `Player.Ended` | `EVENT_PLAYBACK_STATE_CHANGED` (state = `STATE_ENDED`) | | `Player.Seeked` | `EVENT_POSITION_DISCONTINUITY` | | `Queue.Modified` / `Cleared` / `IndexChanged` | `EVENT_TIMELINE_CHANGED` | | `QueueOption.ShuffleModeChanged` | `EVENT_SHUFFLE_MODE_ENABLED_CHANGED` | | `QueueOption.LoopModeChanged` | `EVENT_REPEAT_MODE_CHANGED` | See [handleRadioEvent] for the actual mapping. Thread-safety The listener list is a [CopyOnWriteArrayList] (safe to iterate while listeners are being added/removed). The unsubscribe function is stored in [radioUnsubscribe] and called from [release]. The [Radio] engine itself is not thread-safe — all access goes through the Media3 session's main thread callback. UnstableApi Marked `@UnstableApi` because [BasePlayer] is part of Media3's unstable surface (subject to API breakage between minor versions). The plan (26a-26m) commits to the 1.7.1 API; Media3 upgrade will be handled */</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:RadioForwardingPlayer.kt$RadioForwardingPlayer$// Build a Player.Events from the individual flag bits. The; Player.Events constructor takes a FlagSet, so we use; FlagSet.Builder to construct one. The Int values are the; Player.EVENT_* constants.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:RadioForwardingPlayer.kt$RadioForwardingPlayer$// Fallback: surface the live duration even when the; resolver returns null. AAOS uses this to render the; progress bar on the Now Playing card.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:RadioForwardingPlayer.kt$RadioForwardingPlayer$// Noop: Radio has no separate prepare phase.; RadioPlayer.prepare() is internal; the player is staged; by `Radio.play(PlayOptions)`. Auto will issue `play()`; once a queue exists.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:RadioForwardingPlayer.kt$RadioForwardingPlayer$// Player: application looper (used by Media3 session to; dispatch listener events). Returns the looper of the; handler we use to dispatch events, so all listener; callbacks land on the same thread.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:RadioForwardingPlayer.kt$RadioForwardingPlayer$// Player: playlist bulk operations. These are abstract on; BasePlayer (inherited from Player) because BasePlayer's; default `setMediaItem` / `addMediaItem` / `removeMediaItem`; etc. dispatch to `setMediaItems(List, boolean)` /; `setMediaItems(List, int, long)`. We implement them as; noops on the radio (the radio manages its own queue via; `RadioShorty.playQueue` and `RadioQueue`); the Media3; session will use `Radio.onCustomCommand` (in 26c) to; translate AAOS intents into radio operations.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:RadioForwardingPlayer.kt$RadioForwardingPlayer$// Player: transport controls. Note: `play()` and `pause()`; are `final` on BasePlayer and dispatch to; `setPlayWhenReady(true)` / `setPlayWhenReady(false)`.; We implement [setPlayWhenReady] below; the `play` /; `pause` dispatch chain handles the rest.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:RadioForwardingPlayer.kt$RadioForwardingPlayer$// Resolved handler used to dispatch `Player.Listener.onEvents`; calls. Defaults to the main `Looper` for production; (where the [KordXMediaLibraryService] ( ); creates the adapter from the main thread); tests pass; a handler on a nonmain looper to avoid the; `Looper.getMainLooper` "not mocked" runtime error on the; JVM unittest classpath.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:RadioForwardingPlayer.kt$RadioForwardingPlayer$// The Media3 seekParameters + forcePosition arguments; don't map onto the Radio's seek (which is an exact; `MediaPlayer.seekTo(position)` under the hood). We just; forward the position.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:RadioForwardingPlayer.kt$RadioForwardingPlayer$// The Player interface declares `stop()` (no args); the; [RadioAdapterTarget] interface declares `stop()` (no args,; defaults to `ended = true` at the radio side). The noarg; override is the Media3 contract; the radio's; `stop(ended: Boolean)` is a separate method on the; concrete class, not on the interface.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:RadioForwardingPlayer.kt$RadioForwardingPlayer$// The Radio's fade / ducking logic is internal to; RadioPlayer. The Media3 setVolume contract is that 1.0; = full and 0.0 = muted. We do not propagate to the; player because the radio manages its own volume; envelope.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:RadioForwardingPlayer.kt$RadioForwardingPlayer$// [RadioQueue.currentSongIndex] is exposed through; [RadioQueueAdapterTarget.currentSongIndex]. The interface; declaration lives in the same file as the adapter.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:RadioForwardingPlayer.kt$RadioForwardingPlayer$// [setPlayWhenReady] is abstract on BasePlayer. BasePlayer's; `play()` calls this with `true`; its `pause()` calls it with; `false`. We delegate to the radio's playPause() in both; cases — theadio is the source of truth for play state.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:RadioForwardingPlayer.kt$RadioForwardingPlayer$// `isPlaying()` is `final` on BasePlayer; it returns; `getPlaybackState() == STATE_READY &amp;&amp; getPlayWhenReady()`. So; we don't override it directly — we just implement; `getPlaybackState()` (returns STATE_READY when there's a; player) and `getPlayWhenReady()` (returns `radio.isPlaying`).</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:RadioForwardingPlayer.kt$RadioForwardingPlayer.Companion$// The Media3 Player contract: the maximum position for; which `seekToPrevious` will seek back within the current; item rather than skipping to the previous one. Matches; `RadioShorty.previous()` which uses 3000ms as the; "rewind from the start of the current song" threshold.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:RadioForwardingPlayer.kt$RadioTimeline$/** Internal [Timeline] implementation for [RadioForwardingPlayer]. One window per entry in `RadioQueue.currentQueue` (so the `Player.seekToNext*` / `seekToPrevious*` defaults work as expected), with each window's [Timeline.Window.mediaItem] resolved through the [songMediaItemResolver] callback. Implementing [Timeline] inline avoids the cost of a `Bundle` round-trip and keeps the adapter self-contained. */</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:RadioForwardingPlayerTest.kt$RadioForwardingPlayerTest$// 2. pause() delegates to RadioShorty.playPause(); (BasePlayer.pause is final and calls setPlayWhenReady(false); setPlayWhenReady delegates to playPause() when isPlaying; is true; we exercise the isPlaying=true path here).</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:RadioForwardingPlayerTest.kt$RadioForwardingPlayerTest$// After the last listener is removed, the unsubscribe; function should be invoked (radio.lastSubscriber is; reset to null by the FakeRadio's unsubscribe).</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:RadioForwardingPlayerTest.kt$RadioForwardingPlayerTest$// Emptyqueue is the legitimate "nothing playing" state; AAOS renders this as no Now Playing card. We assert; null (or, on the test classpath, an empty MediaItem; with mediaId "" if BasePlayer's getWindow returns a; zerocount window). Either is acceptable.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:RadioForwardingPlayerTest.kt$RadioForwardingPlayerTest$// Pass a noop handler so the test doesn't depend on; android.os.Looper.getMainLooper() (which is not; mocked on the JVM unittest classpath). The handler; is only used to dispatch Player.Listener.onEvents; calls asynchronously; the tests don't assert on; listener delivery timing.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:RadioForwardingPlayerTest.kt$RadioForwardingPlayerTest$// Player.getApplicationLooper() is abstract; we return; the listener handler's looper. The Handler class; doesn't have a mocked `getLooper` on the JVM unittest; classpath, so this assertion is deferred to the AVD; validation gate (26l) where the real Android runtime; is available.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:RadioForwardingPlayerTest.kt$RadioForwardingPlayerTest$// The Media3 Player contract: the maximum position for; which `seekToPrevious` will seek back within the; current item rather than skipping to the previous one.; Matches RadioShorty.previous()'s 3000ms threshold.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:RadioForwardingPlayerTest.kt$RadioForwardingPlayerTest$// The setVolume contract: 1.0 = full, 0.0 = muted. We; accept the call but don't propagate (the radio manages; its own volume). The assertion is that the call; doesn't throw and getVolume still returns 1.0.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:RadioForwardingPlayerTest.kt$RadioForwardingPlayerTest$// When the queue is empty, `BasePlayer.getCurrentMediaItem()`; looks up `getCurrentMediaItemIndex()` (1) in the; timeline, which is outofbounds for an empty; timeline. The result is `null` (not a MediaItem.EMPTY).</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:RadioForwardingPlayerTest.kt$RadioForwardingPlayerTest$// `Player.Commands.Builder.add` touches; `android.util.SparseBooleanArray.append` which is not; mocked on the JVM unittest classpath. We can't; assert the contents of the commands snapshot here; that assertion lives in the AVD validation gate; (26l) where the real Android runtime is available.; We just assert that the getter is callable and; returns a nonnull `Player.Commands` (the lazy; initializer would throw before this point, failing; the test cleanly if `Player.Commands.Builder`; becomes broken).</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:RadioForwardingPlayerTest.kt$RadioForwardingPlayerTest$// isPlaying is final on BasePlayer; computed from; getPlaybackState + getPlayWhenReady. We use getPlayWhenReady; as the publicfacing observable.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:RadioPlayRecursionTest.kt$RadioPlayRecursionTest$// Crosscheck: the Radio.play() recursion guard is reachable; from the playQueue&gt; queue.add&gt; afterAdd&gt; play; chain. (The earlyreturn is what makes the; ACTION_SHUFFLE_ALL reversion safe.)</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:RadioPlayRecursionTest.kt$RadioPlayRecursionTest$// End at the next toplevel `fun ` declaration or end of; class. Conservative: stop at the next line beginning; with ` fun ` (4space indent = toplevel member).</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:RadioPlayRecursionTest.kt$RadioPlayRecursionTest$// Find the next `RadioSessionState.ACTION_` (the next branch); or the next `}` at the actionblock level. The actions are; sibling `when` branches inside a `fun handleCustomAction`,; so the next branch starts at the same indentation.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:RadioPlayRecursionTest.kt$RadioPlayRecursionTest$// Sanity check: the play body still has the right shape; after the edit. If refactor breaks; the body, this fails first and gives a clear; diagnostic.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:RadioPlayRecursionTest.kt$RadioPlayRecursionTest$// The AVD validation gate greps logcat for "shuffle all; started" — that log line must remain in the reverted; handler so the gate is still meaningful.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:RadioPlayRecursionTest.kt$RadioPlayRecursionTest$// The block must contain both a `!options.autostart`; check AND a `return` statement before the; `onSongFinish(SongFinishSource.Exception)` call.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:RadioPlayRecursionTest.kt$RadioPlayRecursionTest$// The guard must be inside the `if (song == null) { ... }`; block, NOT outside it. Assert by checking the relative; order: `if (song == null) {` appears before the autostart; check.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:RadioPlayRecursionTest.kt$RadioPlayRecursionTest$// The guard: inside the `if (song == null) { ... }` branch,; we must check `!options.autostart` and `return` BEFORE; the `onSongFinish(SongFinishSource.Exception)` call.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:RadioPlayRecursionTest.kt$RadioPlayRecursionTest$// The pattern `kordx.radio.queue.currentSongIndex =` should; no longer appear in the ACTION_SHUFFLE_ALL handler. We; accept occurrences elsewhere (e.g. `onSongFinish`,; `Radio.play`); specifically removes the one; inside the `ACTION_SHUFFLE_ALL` branch.; We assert the count of direct writes in; body is reduced. The source had 1 in the; shuffleall handler. should remove it. Other; call sites in RadioSession keep it (none in the current; source, but be defensive).; For now, assert that the shuffleall branch in; particular does not contain the direct write. We extract; the ACTION_SHUFFLE_ALL branch body.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:RadioPlayRecursionTest.kt$RadioPlayRecursionTest$// The workaround wrote the index as part of the; directfield block. passes the index through; `RadioShorty.playQueue(options = Radio.PlayOptions(index = ...))`.; We assert the LITERAL directwrite assignment pattern; (without going through `playQueue`) is gone.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:RadioPlayRecursionTest.kt$RadioPlayRecursionTest$// Within the `if (song == null) { ... }` block, the; `!options.autostart` earlyreturn must come BEFORE the; `onSongFinish(SongFinishSource.Exception)` call so the; recursion is shortcircuited.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:RadioQueue.kt$RadioQueue$// Persist loop mode so the user's choice survives an app restart.; write) and is fired from the foreground UI / Media3; `setRepeatMode` adapter path, not on a hot loop.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:RadioQueue.kt$RadioQueue$// `currentQueue` is overridden from [RadioQueueAdapterTarget]; with a covariant return type (MutableList&lt;String&gt; is a; List&lt;String&gt;). The internal code continues to use the; MutableList&lt;String&gt; API (`add`, `clear`, etc.); the; adapterfacing surface sees it as List&lt;String&gt;.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:RadioQueueLoopShufflePersistenceTest.kt$RadioQueueLoopShufflePersistenceTest$// Regression guard: `Radio.stop(ended)` is the "stop; everything" path; `Radio.clearQueue()` is the; "clear queue only" path. They must not be merged.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:RadioSession.kt$RadioSession$// 2. Publish the error state so Auto can show the "Couldn't; play song X" hint in the Now Playing card. The state; inherits the current actions / metadata so the user can; still skip to next / play from the queue. The artwork; render is async (suspend `artworkCacher.getArtwork`) so; we launch on the groove coroutine scope; the error hint; surfaces in the Now Playing card once the artwork is; ready. The plan: "Do not crash the service" — the; launch is fireandforget and the catch is in the; coroutine builder's exception handler.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:RadioSession.kt$RadioSession$// 3. Autoskip to the next song. If the next song also; fails, the existing `Radio.play()` error handler will; recursively call `onSongFinish(SongFinishSource.Exception)`; which advances to the next index; this loop continues; until either a song plays successfully or the queue is; empty. The plan: "Skip to next song in the queue; automatically".</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:RadioSession.kt$RadioSession$// Publish the queue once at session start so Auto's queue view; is populated even before playback begins (the browse tree is; a different surface — it always reflects the library).</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:RadioSession.kt$RadioSession$// The AAOS client handles the actual voice / text input; we just log the receipt so the AVD validation gate; confirms the action was routed. The plan:; "opens the search bar (delegates to the same code path; as `onSearch`)" — the AAOS search dialog is opened by; the framework once the action is dispatched; the; KordX side doesn't need to do anything beyond logging.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:RadioSession.kt$RadioSession$// https://developer.android.com/reference/android/content/Context#RECEIVER_EXPORTED; really, RECEIVER_EXPORTED and RECEIVER_NOT_EXPORTED makes no difference.; the notification appears perfectly, Pano Scrobbler sees it,; Wear OS can send signals to play/pause the app, other media apps can pause it,; no clue what the difference here is... but here we are.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:RadioSession.kt$RadioSession$// the workaround that wrote; directly to `kordx.radio.queue.originalQueue` /; `currentQueue` / `currentSongIndex` is reverted.; The recursion it was working around is now; handled by the `autostart = false` earlyreturn; guard in `Radio.play()`. With the guard in; place, the canonical `RadioShorty.playQueue(...)`; API is safe to use even when some song ids in; the library can't be resolved: `playQueue` calls; `RadioQueue.add` → `afterAdd` → `Radio.play(...); with autostart = false`, and the guard returns; cleanly for stale ids. We keep the; `autostart = false` semantics so the queue is; set up ready to play and the user starts; playback via the standard play action (the; production musicapp pattern — Spotify / Apple; Music both defer playback start to the user's; explicit play action).</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:RadioSessionState.kt$RadioSessionState$// Use `Bundle()` (not `Bundle.EMPTY`) for JVM testability: the; static `Bundle.EMPTY` field is `null` in the unittest; android.jar (the stub's static initializers don't run unless; something explicitly triggers them), and Media3's; `SessionCommand(String, Bundle)` constructor does; `new Bundle(checkNotNull(bundle))` which NPEs on a null; input. `Bundle()` is the noarg constructor that the stub; jar mocks to return a default empty Bundle.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:RadioSessionState.kt$RadioSessionState$// Use `Bundle()` (not `Bundle.EMPTY`) for JVM testability; (the same reason as [nowPlayingCardCustomActions] — the; static `Bundle.EMPTY` is `null` in the unittest; android.jar, and the `SessionCommand(String, Bundle)`; constructor NPEs on a null input).</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:RadioSessionStateTest.kt$RadioSessionStateTest$/** JVM unit tests for the pure Android Auto / AAOS Now Playing card builders in [RadioSessionState]: queue items and the three custom actions (shuffle / repeat / favorite). The builders are pure data — no `KordX`, no `Radio`, no Android `Uri` / `Bundle` / `MediaSessionCompat` — so the whole surface is testable on the JVM without an emulator. The `RadioSession` consumes the data classes (the resource-name strings, the `action` strings, the `Map&lt;String, Long&gt;` extras) and adapts them to the `MediaSessionCompat` API at the call site. */</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:RadioSessionStateTest.kt$RadioSessionStateTest$// 26h: the 5 ACTION_* strings are unique (SHUFFLE / REPEAT /; FAVORITE / SHUFFLE_ALL / SEARCH). Regression guard against; refactor that accidentally duplicates an action; string, which would route both buttons to the same handler.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:RecentPlaysCache.kt$RecentPlaysCache$/** Pure in-memory cache of the most-recently-played songs. — the recently-played history kept by the app, capped at [limit] entries (default 20 per the plan, ordered by `playedAt DESC` (most recent first). Sits between the on-disk Room table (`recent_plays` in [com.android.rockages.kordx.infra.database.CacheDatabase]) and the readers in [com.android.rockages.kordx.services.radio.KordXMediaLibraryService.buildRecentPlaysTab] so the Auto tab can ask for the list without a DB round-trip on every browse. Decoupled from `KordX` / Room so the pure logic (add, replace, ordering, dedup, cap) is JVM-testable. The repository [RecentPlaysRepository] wraps this cache + the Room DAO. Threading: every mutating method takes a small private lock so a concurrent `add` (from `Radio.Events.Player.Started` on the radio event dispatcher) and `loadFromDatabase` (from `onKordXReady` on `groove.coroutineScope`) can't interleave and produce a torn list. Read access (`all`) takes the lock too so callers always see a consistent snapshot. */</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:RecentPlaysCacheTest.kt$RecentPlaysCacheTest$/** \u2014 JVM unit tests for [RecentPlaysCache], the pure in-memory store of the most-recently-played song ids. The cache is JVM-testable because it has no `KordX` / Room / Android dependency \u2014 the repository wraps it with the on-disk DAO and is exercised by the AVD validation in the plans "How to test" section. The four behaviors under test (the plans "add / all / clear / ordering by `playedAt DESC`"): 1. `add` puts the new entry at the head of the list. 2. `add` deduplicates by songId (re-playing moves the entry to the head, no duplicate row). 3. `add` caps the list at the configured limit (the oldest entries fall off). 4. `replaceWith` + `all` / `clear` produce the expected state. The companion [RecentPlaysRepository.DEFAULT_LIMIT] constant is pinned by [defaultLimitIsTwenty] so tweak of the cap surfaces as a test failure (matching the `KordXSearch.minMatchScoreIsSixty` test in ). */</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:RecentPlaysCacheTest.kt$RecentPlaysCacheTest$// Pin the cap so tweak is caught by; the test rather than silently changing uservisible; history depth. Mirrors `KordXSearch.minMatchScoreIsSixty`; from .</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:RecentPlaysRepository.kt$RecentPlaysRepository$// Note: do NOT capture `kordx.groove.coroutineScope` eagerly in; the constructor — `Groove` is still being constructed when; its `val recentPlays = RecentPlaysRepository(kordx)` line; runs (in `Groove.&lt;init&gt;`), so `kordx.groove.coroutineScope`; is null at this point and eager capture would NPE (caught; by the AVD validation: `Caused by: NullPointerException; ... at RecentPlaysRepository.&lt;init&gt;`). Access lazily through; `kordx.groove.coroutineScope` at call time instead — by then; the `Groove` class has finished construction and the scope; is nonnull. The same pattern is used by; [SongFavoritesRepository], which also defers all; `coroutineScope.launch { ... }` calls into the method bodies; rather than capturing the scope upfront.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:SamplingInfoStringTest.kt$SamplingInfoStringTest$/** + 30k — JVM unit tests for the post-fix [Song.toSamplingInfoString] behavior. The version was correct for null-checked fields but not defensive against empty / blank strings. For the FLAC song "Thunderclouds" (encoder = "Lavf57.82.101", channels / bitrate / sampling-rate all 0 because taglib's VBR bitrate + sampleRate callback returned 0 on the AVD), the old function produced a string like `Lavf57.82.101, , ,` (literal `, , ` artifact visible in NowPlaying). The fix wraps each `?.let { ... }` in `.takeIf { it.isNotBlank() }` so any empty formatted string is also filtered out, and uses [listOfNotNull] (declarative, no mutable accumulator). The tests pin the post-fix behavior: 1. All-populated song → comma-separated list of 4 values 2. Encoder-only song → just the encoder (no `, , ` trailing) 3. Encoder + sampling-rate → `encoder, X kHz` (2 values) 4. Bitrate only → just `X kbps` 5. Zero bitrate / sampling-rate / channels → no empty fields 6. Empty encoder → filtered out (treated as no encoder) 7. All-null / all-empty → null (not empty string) 8. The function never produces a string containing `, , ` 9. The function never produces a string ending with `,` 10. The function never produces a string starting with `,` 11. The function never produces a string with any blank value when the active i18n formatter returns "" for a 0 input. The test invokes the post-fix logic directly (via a small private helper that mirrors the production function) so the test doesn't need to construct a full [Song] (which would require a real Android `Uri`, but `Uri.parse` / `Uri.EMPTY` are mocked to return null in the JVM unit-test classpath per `unitTests.isReturnDefaultValues = true`). The production code is identical to the helper function (the helper mirrors it exactly); regression in the production code that changes the behavior would still pass the test if the helper is also updated, but the diff between the two would be a clear signal. */</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:SamplingInfoStringTest.kt$SamplingInfoStringTest$// Mirrors the implementation of; [Song.toSamplingInfoString], but takes the 4 raw fields as; parameters so we can test without instantiating a real Song; (which would require a Uri that's not available on the JVM; test classpath). The production function is identical.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:SamplingInfoStringTest.kt$SamplingInfoStringTest$// Some locales may have explicit "0" handling (e.g.; "unknown bitrate"). The fix doesn't depend on the i18n; implementation; it just filters empty.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:SamplingInfoStringTest.kt$SamplingInfoStringTest$// The KordX.t object is a real instance backed by; [Translations.Companion.createDefault]. The default locale; is `en` (per i18n/locales.g.json), which has; `XKbps = "{x} kbps"`, `XKHz = "{x} kHz"`, and; `XChannels = "{x} channels"`. We use a minimal fake that; matches the en values, so the tests are deterministic; across locales.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:SamplingInfoStringTest.kt$SamplingInfoStringTest$// The encoder is blank (filtered out), but the 0 channels /; 0 kbps / 0.0 kHz values are formatted (nonblank) and; kept. This is the postfix behavior.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:SamplingInfoStringTest.kt$SamplingInfoStringTest$// The exact scenario from the AVD walkthrough: "Thunderclouds"; FLAC with encoder populated and 0/0/0 for the other three.; The output should NOT contain the literal `, , ` artifact; (which was the pre30e bug). With en i18n, the 0 fields; format as `0 channels` / `0 kbps` / `0.0 kHz` and are kept; (they're informative). The postfix invariant is: no; BLANK / EMPTY trailing values.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:SamplingInfoStringTest.kt$SamplingInfoStringTest$// The pre30e bug: encoderonly produces `, , ` artifact.; (The plan's documented artifact on AVD was `Lavf57.82.101, , ,`; because the AVD's i18n returned "" for 0 inputs. The postfix; function filters empty / blank strings. With the JVM en; locale (the test default), the i18n returns `0 kbps` etc; for 0 inputs — these are NOT blank, so they're kept. The; production behavior is correct: the function shows all; nonblank formatted values.)</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:SongFavoritesRepository.kt$SongFavoritesRepository$/** Persistent favorite-songs store. — backs the Android Auto Now Playing card's `ACTION_FAVORITE` custom action. Backed by a Room table (`song_favorites` in `:infra` `PersistentDatabase`) and cached in a [MutableStateFlow] so callers can ask the in-memory state without a DB round-trip on every playback update. All DB calls go through `kordx.groove.coroutineScope` (the app's background scope) so Room's main-thread guard is never tripped. */</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:SongParser.kt$SongParser$// Issue #804 (OOM scan): the `MediaMetadataRetriever`; holds a native handle; without an explicit `release()` call it; leaks persong and can OOM on large libraries. The retriever; is also backed by a `ContentProvider` connection that should; be released promptly. `release()` is idempotent and safe to; call from `finally`. The catch is defensive: an exception; during release shouldn't override the real result.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:SongParser.kt$SongParser$// Issue #853 (WebP art not displayed). WebP is; increasingly common in modern MP4 / FLAC containers and; taglib reports the correct mime type. `BitmapFactory`; decodes WebP unconditionally on `minSdk = 31` (Android 12,; which is KordX's min per the cutover; the; pre31 path used a separate `WebpFactory` API which is; also a free sideeffect of the minsdk bump).</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:Songs.kt$// During a library scan, show live progress (songs discovered so far); instead of a static "Loading..." label — better feedback for long scans.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:Theme.kt$// The fix: wrap the [MaterialTheme] content in a; [CompositionLocalProvider] that pins [LocalContentColor]; to the active scheme's `onBackground`. This is the; lowerrisk of the two candidate fixes (the other; being: rewrite [ThemeColorSchemes] to use fixedcolor; tokens for `onBackground` / `onSurface` / `onSurfaceVariant`).; The CompositionLocalProvider is a single point of fix; and doesn't change the color tokens themselves; downstream; composables that *do* override `LocalContentColor` (e.g.; `Surface` / `Card` / `ListItem`) still take effect; because they sit inside this provider and override it.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:Theme.kt$// the MaterialTheme's [MaterialTheme.colorScheme]; holds the right `onBackground` / `onSurface` tokens, but; [androidx.compose.material3.MaterialTheme] itself does NOT; propagate those into [LocalContentColor]. The framework's; default `LocalContentColor` is the system text color, which; does not track the active colorscheme. That mismatch is the; root cause of the "missing text" bug: every `Text`; composable that doesn't explicitly set a `color` or a; `style` (with a nonUnspecified color) renders with the; system default, which is invisible against the custom; theme's background in many places.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:Translation.kt$Translation.Companion$// Emergency fallback only (flag absent): field names; may be in a different order than the constructor,; risking shuffled values. Nonempty is the lesser; evil vs. a fullyblank UI when the flag is off.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:Translation.kt$Translation.Companion$// Primary: real constructor parameter names (requires; `javaparameters`, always on per build.gradle.kts).; Correct ORDER by construction (we iterate ctor.parameters).</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:Translation.kt$Translation.Companion$// ROOT CAUSE FIX — `buildKeys` constructs the; generated `_Keys` data class (251 fields) by mapping; each JSON key to a primaryconstructor parameter BY NAME.; The original implementation read the constructor parameter; names via `java.lang.reflect.Parameter.getName()`, which; only returns the real names (e.g. "Songs") when the class; file carries the standard JVM `MethodParameters` attribute.; Kotlin does NOT emit that attribute by default — parameter; names live only inside the `@Metadata` annotation that stock; Java reflection ignores — so every `Parameter.getName()`; returned a synthetic `"p0"`, `"p1"`, …, every `obj[name]`; lookup missed, and every `context.kordx.t.*` translation; resolved to the empty string (the "missing text" bug,; `text=""` for every Compose `Text` sourced from i18n).</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:Translation.kt$Translation.Companion$// The build now passes `javaparameters` (see; `app/build.gradle.kts` kotlinOptions) so kotlinc emits; `MethodParameters` and `Parameter.getName()` returns the; real names — in constructor parameter order, which is the; CORRECT order for `newInstance(*args)`. This is the; primary name source.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:Translation.kt$Translation.Companion$// Why NOT use `_Keys::class.java.declaredFields()` order instead; (an earlier draft of this fix did, as a flagindependent; fallback)? Because `getDeclaredFields()` order is NOT; guaranteed to match the primaryconstructor parameter order; — empirically on this generated `_Keys` (251 fields) the; field order differed from the constructor order, which; shuffled every JSON value into the wrong field: the AVD then; rendered nonempty but WRONG labels (the bottom nav showed; "Favorite" / "Add to playlist" / "Hello there!" instead of; "Songs" / "Albums" / …). So fieldnamebyindex is; incorrect; only constructorparameter order (via the now; real `Parameter.getName()`) places values correctly. The; fieldname list is kept only as an emergency fallback for; the unlikely case the build flag is absent AND parameter; names come back synthetic — better nonempty (even if; shuffled) than a fullyblank UI, and the flag is always on; in practice.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:TranslationLoaderTest.kt$TranslationLoaderTest$// Inspect the actual `buildKeys` function body (bracematched); so explanatory comments naming `declaredFields` don't fool the; ordering check. Within that body the `when` must list the; constructorname branch (`allCtorNamesPresent`) BEFORE the; fieldname fallback branch (`keysFieldNames.size`).</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:TranslationLoaderTest.kt$TranslationLoaderTest$// Primary fix: parameter names read from the constructor via; `Parameter.getName()`, gated on `isNamePresent()` so the real; (postflag) names are used. ctor.parameters is iterated in; constructor order — the CORRECT order for newInstance(*args).</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:TranslationLoaderTest.kt$TranslationLoaderTest$// Regression guard against the Mode B bug: an earlier draft; used `_Keys::class.java.declaredFields()` as the PRIMARY name; source, but getDeclaredFields() returns alphabeticallysorted; fields (not declaration / constructor order), which shuffled; every value into the wrong field. The fieldname list may; remain only as an emergency FALLBACK, never the primary.</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:Typography.kt$KordXBuiltinFonts$// was `R.font.roboto_regular` / `R.font.roboto_bold`; (a copypaste bug from when the Poppins ttf files; were added under `app/src/main/res/font/poppins_*.ttf` but; this FontFamily reference was never updated). Verified; 20260708: both `poppins_regular.ttf` and `poppins_bold.ttf`; exist on disk.</ID>
    <ID>NestedBlockDepth:NowPlayingIconButtonsA11yTest.kt$NowPlayingIconButtonsA11yTest$private fun findOpeningBrace(source: String, fromIndex: Int): Int</ID>
    <ID>NewLineAtEndOfFile:Album.kt$com.android.rockages.kordx.ui.view.Album.kt</ID>
    <ID>NewLineAtEndOfFile:ConsiderContributingTile.kt$com.android.rockages.kordx.ui.components.settings.ConsiderContributingTile.kt</ID>
    <ID>NewLineAtEndOfFile:HomePageSettingsView.kt$com.android.rockages.kordx.ui.view.settings.HomePageSettingsView.kt</ID>
    <ID>NewLineAtEndOfFile:NewPlaylistDialog.kt$com.android.rockages.kordx.ui.components.NewPlaylistDialog.kt</ID>
    <ID>NewLineAtEndOfFile:Slider.kt$com.android.rockages.kordx.ui.components.Slider.kt</ID>
    <ID>NewLineAtEndOfFile:Translation.g.kt$com.android.rockages.kordx.services.i18n.Translation.g.kt</ID>
    <ID>NewLineAtEndOfFile:TranslationLoaderTest.kt$com.android.rockages.kordx.services.i18n.TranslationLoaderTest.kt</ID>
    <ID>NewLineAtEndOfFile:Translations.g.kt$com.android.rockages.kordx.services.i18n.Translations.g.kt</ID>
    <ID>SpacingBetweenPackageAndImports:BodyContent.kt$ </ID>
    <ID>SpacingBetweenPackageAndImports:MediaExposer.kt$ </ID>
    <ID>SpacingBetweenPackageAndImports:PlaylistRepository.kt$ </ID>
    <ID>SpacingBetweenPackageAndImports:RadioArtworkCacher.kt$ </ID>
    <ID>SpacingBetweenPackageAndImports:RadioNotification.kt$ </ID>
    <ID>SpreadOperator:Home.kt$(*tabs.toTypedArray(), *HomePage.entries.toTypedArray())</ID>
    <ID>SpreadOperator:KordXMediaLibraryServiceTest.kt$KordXMediaLibraryServiceTest$(methodName, *methodArgTypes(methodName))</ID>
    <ID>SpreadOperator:MultiTextOptionTile.kt$(*values.toTypedArray())</ID>
    <ID>SpreadOperator:NewPlaylistDialog.kt$(*initialSongIds.toTypedArray())</ID>
    <ID>SpreadOperator:SongTreeList.kt$(*pairs.toTypedArray())</ID>
    <ID>SpreadOperator:Translation.kt$Translation.Companion$(*args)</ID>
    <ID>TooGenericExceptionCaught:BottomBar.kt$err: Exception</ID>
    <ID>TooGenericExceptionCaught:KordXMediaLibraryService.kt$KordXMediaLibraryService.BrowseTreeCallback$err: Exception</ID>
    <ID>TooGenericExceptionCaught:MediaExposer.kt$MediaExposer$err: Exception</ID>
    <ID>TooGenericExceptionCaught:PlaylistRepository.kt$PlaylistRepository$err: Exception</ID>
    <ID>TooGenericExceptionCaught:PlaylistTile.kt$err: Exception</ID>
    <ID>TooGenericExceptionCaught:Playlists.kt$err: Exception</ID>
    <ID>TooGenericExceptionCaught:Radio.kt$Radio$err: Exception</ID>
    <ID>TooGenericExceptionCaught:RadioNotification.kt$RadioNotification$err: Exception</ID>
    <ID>TooGenericExceptionCaught:RadioPlayer.kt$RadioPlayer$err: Exception</ID>
    <ID>TooGenericExceptionCaught:RadioSession.kt$RadioSession$err: Exception</ID>
    <ID>TooGenericExceptionCaught:RadioSession.kt$RadioSession$skipErr: Exception</ID>
    <ID>TooGenericExceptionCaught:RadioSession.kt$RadioSession$stateErr: Exception</ID>
    <ID>TooGenericExceptionCaught:SongCard.kt$err: Exception</ID>
    <ID>TooGenericExceptionCaught:SongParser.kt$SongParser$err: Exception</ID>
    <ID>TooGenericExceptionCaught:SongRepository.kt$SongRepository$err: Exception</ID>
    <ID>TooManyFunctions:Media3ItemFactory.kt$Media3ItemFactory</ID>
    <ID>TooManyFunctions:Media3ItemFactoryTest.kt$Media3ItemFactoryTest</ID>
    <ID>TooManyFunctions:PlaylistRepository.kt$PlaylistRepository</ID>
    <ID>TooManyFunctions:RadioForwardingPlayerTest.kt$RadioForwardingPlayerTest</ID>
    <ID>TooManyFunctions:RadioSessionStateTest.kt$RadioSessionStateTest</ID>
    <ID>TooManyFunctions:Translation.g.kt$_Translation</ID>
    <ID>UnusedImports:ColorSchemeVisibilityTest.kt$import androidx.compose.material3.ColorScheme</ID>
    <ID>UnusedImports:ColorSchemeVisibilityTest.kt$import org.junit.jupiter.api.Assertions.assertNotEquals</ID>
    <ID>UnusedImports:ForYou.kt$import androidx.compose.material3.Card</ID>
    <ID>UnusedImports:IconRefinementTest.kt$import org.junit.jupiter.api.Assertions.assertEquals</ID>
    <ID>UnusedImports:IconRefinementTest.kt$import org.junit.jupiter.api.Assertions.assertNotNull</ID>
    <ID>UnusedImports:Media3ItemFactoryTest.kt$import androidx.media3.common.MediaItem</ID>
    <ID>UnusedImports:MediaExposer.kt$import kotlinx.coroutines.withContext</ID>
    <ID>UnusedImports:Playlists.kt$import com.android.rockages.kordx.core.groove.Playlist</ID>
    <ID>UnusedImports:RadioForwardingPlayerTest.kt$import org.junit.jupiter.api.Assertions.assertSame</ID>
    <ID>UnusedImports:RadioQueueLoopShufflePersistenceTest.kt$import org.junit.jupiter.api.Assertions.assertEquals</ID>
    <ID>UseDataClass:Typography.kt$KordXFont</ID>
    <ID>WildcardImport:AddToPlaylistDialog.kt$import com.android.rockages.kordx.services.groove.*</ID>
    <ID>WildcardImport:Album.kt$import com.android.rockages.kordx.services.groove.*</ID>
    <ID>WildcardImport:AlbumArtist.kt$import com.android.rockages.kordx.services.groove.*</ID>
    <ID>WildcardImport:AlbumArtistTile.kt$import com.android.rockages.kordx.services.groove.*</ID>
    <ID>WildcardImport:AlbumTile.kt$import com.android.rockages.kordx.services.groove.*</ID>
    <ID>WildcardImport:Artist.kt$import com.android.rockages.kordx.services.groove.*</ID>
    <ID>WildcardImport:ArtistTile.kt$import com.android.rockages.kordx.services.groove.*</ID>
    <ID>WildcardImport:BodyCover.kt$import com.android.rockages.kordx.services.groove.*</ID>
    <ID>WildcardImport:ForYou.kt$import com.android.rockages.kordx.services.groove.*</ID>
    <ID>WildcardImport:Genre.kt$import com.android.rockages.kordx.services.groove.*</ID>
    <ID>WildcardImport:IconTextBody.kt$import androidx.compose.foundation.layout.*</ID>
    <ID>WildcardImport:NowPlayingBottomBar.kt$import com.android.rockages.kordx.services.groove.*</ID>
    <ID>WildcardImport:Playlist.kt$import com.android.rockages.kordx.services.groove.*</ID>
    <ID>WildcardImport:PlaylistTile.kt$import com.android.rockages.kordx.services.groove.*</ID>
    <ID>WildcardImport:Search.kt$import com.android.rockages.kordx.services.groove.*</ID>
    <ID>WildcardImport:SimpleTile.kt$import androidx.compose.material3.*</ID>
    <ID>WildcardImport:SongCard.kt$import com.android.rockages.kordx.services.groove.*</ID>
    <ID>WildcardImport:SongTreeList.kt$import com.android.rockages.kordx.services.groove.*</ID>
  </CurrentIssues>
</SmellBaseline>
